A Guide to the Reedy Creek Baptist Church (Brunswick County, Va.), Minute Books,, 3 March 1898-28 June 1998
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Reedy Creek Baptist Church (Brunswick County, Va.), Minute Books, 3 March 1898-28 June 1998
The Library of Virginia
42247
1 reel
Reedy Creek Baptist Church (Brunswick County, Va.)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Lent for microfilming by Reedy Creek Baptist Church, 25 October 2005
Historical Information
Founded by Zechariah Thompson, Reedy Creek Baptist Church in Brunswick County, Virginia was chartered in 1772. However, it is believed that the church was in existence long before that year. A new church was built in 1956.
Scope and Content
Minute Books, 3 March 1898-28 June 1998, of Reedy Creek Baptist Church in Brunswick County, Virginia. In addition to minutes, the minute books contain lists of members, church officers, and ministers.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Minute Book, 3 March 1898-3 August 1913 (Reel 4841)
  Also includes membership lists.
- Minute Book, 2 May 1914-15 October 1935. (Reel 4841)
  Also includes a resolution regarding church property, the church constitution, and lists of members and church officers.
- Minute Book, 18 January 1936-October 1945. (Reel 4841)
  Also includes membership lists and statistics, and lists of church officers.
- Minute Book, 12 October 1950-21 April 1957. (Reel 4841)
  Also includes lists of members and church officers.
- Minute Book, 5 July 1959-26 August 1960. (Reel 4841)
  Also includes lists of members, church officers, and ministers.
- Minute Book, 23 September 1960-6 September 1968. (Reel 4841)
  Also includes lists of members, church officers and ministers.
- Minute Book, 11 October 1968-3 September 1972. (Reel 4841)
- Minute Book, 22 September 1972-4 January 1980. (Reel 4841)
- Minute Book, 4 April 1980-10 July 1987. (Reel 4841)
- Minute Book, 25 September 1987-28 June 1998. (Reel 4841)